After a night of Russian attacks, the power supply was broken
To the nuclear power plant in Zaporizjzja.
Let me remind you that it is the largest nuclear power plant in Europe
As for the sixth time relying on diesel -powered emergency generators.
Since September, the Russian-occupied nuclear power plant produces no electricity
But all six reactors must be cooled down to prevent meltdown.
For over ten hours, the power plant was driven by reserve generators
before the power came back.
It is a dice throw every time.
If we let it happen time and time again, one day the happiness will turn around.
The Wagner Group has taken control of most of the eastern Bachmut.
At the same time, Ukrainian forces have destroyed important bridges over the Bachmutka river
in the central parts of the city.
The river now marks the front line in the bloody battles
According to the British Department of Defense, which describes the area as a death zone.
It is difficult to go over watercourses if they are larger than a ditch.
It makes it not unusual
That there will be fierce battles precisely at this type of terrain.
But will the Russians, in this case, over the river
It becomes very difficult for the Ukrainians to push them back on the other side.
Therefore, for example, this river is very important for the Ukrainian defense.
Battle of Bachmut has been going on for eight months
And is described as decisive by both Ukraine and Russia.
If Bachmut falls, many Russian soldiers will be full.
They will go down in the basements
Where the wine producers store their sparkling wine.
This celebration will also rely in Russia.
This will then be the first slightly bigger victory
Then on July 3 when you took Lysytjan.
I do not think it will lead to a greater operational breakthrough
where one gets the opportunity from Russian side
Right now it seems that this is getting a diplomatic consequence.
Thus, diplomatic consequences, rather than any form of military.
Ukraine has a lack of ammunition
and in American scranton, nearly 8,000 km from the front
Walks this weapon factory at high speed.
We run full two shifts.
We have a third shift too.
We are running five six days a week.
Pentagon has given US weapons factories on assignment
To equip and increase the production of 155 mm artillery ammunition.
From 170,000 like this in 2021 to over one million a year next year.
Without constant supplement with ammunition and other supplies from the West
Can't Ukrainian Army continue and fight the way you do.
Then the intensity goes down and we end up in a war war clearer.
One must also on the Ukrainian side build up stock
For what you say is the upcoming spring offensive.
When tanks, combat vehicles or artillery should work for
to continue to free the country.